A Guide to the Raven Society Office Administrative Files 1979-1990
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Raven Society Office Administrative Files 1970-1990
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-23/34/3.901
This collection consists of items contained in six boxes.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Fellowship applications are restricted. Contact curator for details.
Acquisition Information
Gift, 27 August 1990.
Contents List
- Biographies (Box 1)
- Biographies 1977-1981 (Box 1)
- Change of Address 1896-1987 (Box 1)
- Correspondence 1984-1985 (Box 1)
- Correspondence 1980-1982 (Box 1)
- Correspondence 1974-1978 (Box 1)
- Correspondence 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  Incoming
- Correspondence 1986 (Box 1)
  Outgoing
- Elections 1986-1988, 2 folders (Box 1)
- Elections 1985-1986 (Box 2)
- Elections 1979-1981 (Box 2)
- Elections and Biographies 1984-1985 (Box 2)
- Elections, Biographies, Parodies 1978 (Box 2)
- Faculty Nominations 1980-1983 (Box 2)
- Farmington (Box 2)
  Paper
- Isaac Alexander Bigger, Jr., M.D. 1986 (Box 2)
  Biographical Sketch
- Master Membership List and Information 1951-1990 (Box 2)
- Members and Fellowship Selections 1987-1988 (Box 2)
- Membership 1986-1988 (Box 2)
- Membership 1972-1988, 8 folders (Box 3)
- Membership 1970-1982 (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous 1978-1987 (Box 4)
- Nominations 1973 (Box 4)
- Parodies (Box 4)
- Parodies 1989-1990 (Box 4)
- Parodies [1971-1988], 3 folders (Box 4)
- Parodies [1977-1982] (Box 5)
- Past Presidents' Letters 1984 (Box 5)
- Pending Raven 1985-1988 (Box 5)
- Raven Awards 1984-1987 (Box 5)
  Alumni Members
- Raven Fellowship Applications 1989 (Box 5)
  RESTRICTED
- Raven Letters 1989 (Box 5)
- Stationery (Box 5)
- Raven Fellowship Applications 1989 (Box 6)